[
  { "back": "すき", "front": "like" },
  { "back": "ハンサム", "front": "handsome" },
  { "back": "きらい", "front": "dislike" },
  { "back": "わかります", "front": "understand" },
  { "back": "じょうず", "front": "good at" },
  { "back": "へた", "front": "bad at" },
  { "back": "りょり", "front": "cooking, cuisine" },
  { "back": "のみもの", "front": "drinks" },
  { "back": "たべもの", "front": "foods" },
  { "back": "おんがく", "front": "music" },
  { "back": "うた", "front": "song" },
  { "back": "え", "front": "picture" },
  { "back": "もしもし", "front": "hello(using on phone)" },
  { "back": "どうして", "front": "why, what is the reason" },
  { "back": "どう", "front": "how" },
  { "back": "ぜんぜん", "front": "not at all" },
  { "back": "すこし", "front": "little bit" },
  { "back": "たくさん", "front": "many, a lot" },
  { "back": "だいたい", "front": "almost, general, substantially, about much" },
  { "back": "くども", "front": "children" },
  { "back": "おくさん", "front": "your wife, his wife, wife" },
  { "back": "うま/かない", "front": "(my) wife" },
  { "back": "おっゅじん", "front": "(my) husband" },
  { "back": "ごしゅじん", "front": "(your) husband" },
  { "back": "やくそく", "front": "promise, agreement" },
  { "back": "ようじ", "front": "tasks, things to do" },
  { "back": "よく", "front": "often, well" },
  { "back": "どんな", "front": "which one" },
  { "back": "から", "front": "because, from" },
  { "back": "はやく", "front": "fast, early, quickly" },
  { "back": "きれい", "front": "beautiful, clean" },
  { "back": "しずか", "front": "quiet" },
  { "back": "にぎやか", "front": "lively" },
  { "back": "ゆうめい", "front": "famous" },
  { "back": "しんせつ", "front": "kind" },
  { "back": "げんき", "front": "healthy, sound, cheerful" },
  { "back": "ひま", "front": "free (time)" },
  { "back": "べんり", "front": "convenient" },
  { "back": "すてき", "front": "fine, nice, wonderful" },
  { "back": "おおきい", "front": "big, large" },
  { "back": "ちいさい", "front": "small, little" },
  { "back": "あたらしい", "front": "new" },
  { "back": "あります", "front": "have" },
  { "back": "やきゅう", "front": "baseball" },
  { "back": "りょこう", "front": "trip" },
  { "back": "じ", "front": "character(language)" },
  { "back": "じかん", "front": "time,  hour" },
  { "back": "ふるい", "front": "old (not of age)" },
  { "back": "いい (よい)", "front": "good" },
  { "back": "わるい", "front": "bad" },
  { "back": "あつい", "front": "hot" },
  { "back": "さむい", "front": "cold (temperature)" },
  { "back": "つめたい", "front": "cold (to the touch)" },
  { "back": "むずかしい", "front": "difficult" },
  { "back": "やさしい", "front": "easy" },
  { "back": "たかい", "front": "expensive, tall, high" },
  { "back": "やすい", "front": "inexpensive" },
  { "back": "ひくい", "front": "low" },
  { "back": "おもしろい", "front": "interesting" },
  { "back": "おいしい", "front": "delicious, tasty" },
  { "back": "いそがしい", "front": "busy" },
  { "back": "たのしい", "front": "enjoyable" },
  { "back": "しろい", "front": "white" },
  { "back": "くろい", "front": "black" },
  { "back": "あかい", "front": "red" },
  { "back": "あおい", "front": "blue" },
  { "back": "さくら", "front": "cherry blossom" },
  { "back": "やま", "front": "mountain" },
  { "back": "まち", "front": "town, city" },
  { "back": "くるま", "front": "car, vehicle" },
  { "back": "ところ", "front": "place" },
  { "back": "りょう", "front": "dormitory" },
  { "back": "べんきょう", "front": "study" },
  { "back": "せいかつ", "front": "life" },
  { "back": "しごと", "front": "work, business" },
  { "back": "どう", "front": "how" },
  { "back": "どんな", "front": "what kind of" },
  { "back": "どれ", "front": "which one (of three or more)" },
  { "back": "とても", "front": "very" },
  { "back": "あまり", "front": "not so (used with negatives)" },
  { "back": "そして", "front": "and (used to connect sentences)" },
  { "back": "が", "front": "~, but ~" }
]